Guide to the Jesse Pyrant Andrews photographs and oral histories, 1973-2020 RL.00043
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Portraits, 1975-2019; 2.2 Linear Feet 48 photographic prints; 48 CD-ROMs; 1 notebook; 22.7 Gigabytes 96 files 48 .wav files; 48 .mp3 files
  - George P. Hunt, Jr. (Toby), South Boston, Virginia, 2017 December 6; 3 items 1 print; 2 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_204, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0039.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0040.WAV)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 172-11
    George Hunt's father was editor of Life magazine from 1960-1968. During this time, Toby worked in the photo lab and equipment room of the magazine and often accompanied Life photographers on assignments as an assistant. He knew the great photographers of that era, Eugene Smith, Ralph Morse, Larry Burroughs, and others. Oral history accompanies this print.
  - Richard Patterson, Pittsylvania County, Virginia, 2018 January; 2 items 1 print; 1 CD (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_206, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0043.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 172-23
    Richard Patterson served as an Army Airborne medic from 1952 until 1978. He spent 1968 and 1969 in the Mekong Delta of Vietnam as a medic with the 25th Infantry during which time he participated in 24 search and destroy missions. He suffers from diabetes as a result of exposure to Agent Orange.
    Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Veteran's Project.
  - Lee Mall, Halifax County, Virginia, 2017 September 29; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_207, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0034.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0035.WAV, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0036.WAV)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 173-7
    Lee Mall served as an infantryman with C Co., 1st Battalion, 46th Division of the 198th Light Infantry Brigade in the Central Highlands of Vietnam from March of 1968 until March of 1969. He was present when LZ Professional was overrun by NVA [North Vietnamese Army] forces.
    Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Veterans Project.
  - John Payne, Lunenburg County, Virginia, 2018 February 21; 5 items 1 print; 4 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_208, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0044.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0045.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0046.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0047.MP3)
    John Payne served as an infantryman with the 1st Air Cavalry, then with the 101st Airborne in the Central Highlands of Vietnam, later in the Mekong Delta south of Saigon. His platoon lost 19 of 25 men in a two day firefight in the A Shau Valley on the 15th April, 1971.
    Two oral histories, recorded by Andrews in separate sessions, accompany this print. Part of the Veterans Project.
  - Fred Behrens, Powhatan, Virginia, 2018 April 5; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_209, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0048.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0049.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0050.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 173-22
    Fred Behrens served with the 326th Medical Battalion of the 101st Airborne Division in the Central Highlands of Vietnam from May of 1970 until June of 1971, first as an assault helicopter pilot and later as a medivac (dustoff) pilot, based at Phu Bai. On 23 April 1971, while flying into an intense firefight in the A Shau valley, his helicopter was shot down. Wounded five times, he hid in the jungle for two days until he was rescued.
  - Chris Cole, Halifax, Virginia, 2017 December 1; 3 items 1 print; 2 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_210, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0037.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0038.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 172-5
    Chris Cole served with the 5th Battalion of the 11th Marine Corps Division during the initial invasion of Iraq in March of 2003.
  - Couple at family reunion, Whittles, Virginia, 2016 June (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_212)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 162-3
  - Bill Jenkins, Rice, Virginia, 2017-2018; 7 items 1 print; 6 CDs (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_213, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0028.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0029.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0030.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0031.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0032.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0033.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 170-31
    Since 1964, Bill Jenkins has operated Jenkin's Blue and Gray Wayside, a general/convenience store established by his grandfather in the 1950s. Bill is an exceptionally friendly man who has met and befriended people from all over the world while operating the store. He is a fascinating story teller and loves talking about the people he has met as well as his dedication to and involvement in his community. Stores like Jenkin's and people of Bill's open and accepting nature are fast becoming a part of history.
    Two-part oral history accompanies this print, conducted by Andrews on September 22, 2017 (RL00043-CD-0028 to -0030) and February 13, 2018 (RL00043-CD-0031 to -0033).
  - Bob Cage at his farm, Shanti, Halifax County, Virginia, 2011 July (Box 12, Image RL00043_P_214)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 145-28
    Bob Cage grew up in Halifax, Virginia, serving in the Marine Corps during WW2. He later became a nationally ranked tennis player, and won the world's championship tobacco auctioneering contest in 1984. He was a prolific painter and sculptor, working primarily with found materials. His paintings and sculptures can be seen around Halifax and South Boston. He was a key figure in the fight against uranium mining in Virginia. He died in 2014 at age 91.
  - Donald Wright, Tightsqueeze, Virginia, 2018 May 1; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 13, Image RL00043_P_215, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0051.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0052.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0053.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 174 7a-8
    Served in the Marine Corps, 1968-1975, first as a squad sergeant with A Co., 1/7th of the 1st Marine Division west of Da Nang, then with the 1st Marine Recon Battalion. Oral history and handwritten account accompany this print. Part of the Vietnam Project.
  - Donald Wright, Vietnam War memoir (1968-1973), 2018; 108 pages 1 spiral-bound notebook 6x9 inches (Box 13)
    Sgt. Donald Wright's memoir begins in September 1968 with his arrival at Da Nang, and ends in 1973 when he re-enlisted. The narrative is sometimes non-linear, jumping from memory to memory. Wright recalls battles, operations, life and leisure at military bases and camps, civilians in the war, Viet Cong attacks, Viet Cong child soldiers, a mine sweep on Liberty Road, a court-martial murder case, being wounded in combat, bonding with other soldiers in the Army, religious reflections, thoughts of home, and homecomings.
    According to his memoir, Sgt. Donald Wright first served as squad leader in the 3rd Guard, 3rd Platoon, Alpha Co. 1/7 1st Marine Division; later, he was promoted to Corporal and became an MP (Military Police). Battles described in detail include Memorial Weekend Battle, Meade River, Lynn River, and the Tet Offensive.
    The memoir is handwritten, with edits and side commentaries. Two sets of loose pages describing other memories are laid in. Also included are a few patches and an undated memorial program for George Alfred Marks, Jr. (1945-1968), member of the 1st Battalion, 7th Marines Division, location of memorial is given as the Republic of Vietnam. Marks died there in November 1968 (Source: Find a Grave website, February 2021).
  - Rev. Donald Wilson, Buffalo Junction, Virginia, 2018 May; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 13, Image RL00043_P_216, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0054.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0055.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0056.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 174-8
    Ordained as a Baptist minister in 1962, Donald Wilson served as Chaplain in the U.S. Army for 26 years. He spent a year with an infantry company at LZ West, near Da Nang, South Vietnam, 1968-69, accompanying them on patrols and into firefights, even though he never carried a weapon. After his service in Vietnam, he served as Chaplain at Army bases around the world, including becoming Chaplain at West Point. Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Vietnam Project.
  - Dianne Gagliano, Charlottesville, Virginia, 2018 November; 5 items 1 photograph; 4 CDs (Box 13, Image RL00043_P_217, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0057.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0058.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0059.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0060.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 175-7
    Colonel Gagliano joined the U.S. Air Force Nurse Corps in 1967. She served for 18 years as a flight nurse in both the Pacific and Atlantic Aeromedical, accruing over 2000 in-flight patient hours. This included six years in Vietnam, evacuating wounded servicemen to hospitals in other countries where they could receive the care they needed. These flights involved gruelling 24-hour days aboard a huge C-141 cargo plane which had been reconfigured with cots, IV poles, and other medical equipment to care for the wounded. Flights carried between 80 and 100 patients. They would fly from the Philippines to Saigon, then to Da Nang, picking up patients along the way; then to Guam, Hawaii, Japan, Alaska, and California, dropping off patients according to their needs, then return to the Philippines. They made two flights a week, typically. She later served as a flight nurse in Operation Desert Storm and in Afghanistan. In all those years, she lost only one patient. She also participated in the airlift of POWs from Hanoi in 1973, as well as in Operation Saigon Baby Lift in 1975, helping to evacuate several thousand orphaned children from South Vietnam, many of whom were children of American servicemen who had served there. Col. Gagliano was also an influential force in the creation and dedication in 1993 of the Women's Memorial in Arlington, Virginia. She retired after 26 years of service. Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Vietnam Project.
  - Rose and Harold Hughes, Virgilina, Virginia, 2018 June; 3 items 1 print; 2 CDs (Box 13, Image RL00043_P_218, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0063.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0064.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 175 8-9a
    Harold Hughes served as an infantryman with the 1/26 Infantry in Vietnam from February 1967 until July 1968. He was severely wounded by mortar fire while on patrol in the Central Highlands. His wife, Rose, initiated an effort to establish a chapter of Vietnam Veterans of America in South Boston, Virginia, as a way of bringing Vietnam vets together. Strength in unity. Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Vietnam Project.
  - Charles Throckmorton, Scottsburg, Virginia, 2018 September; 3 items 1 print; 2 CDs (Box 13, Image RL00043_P_219, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0061.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0062.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 175-35
    Charles Throckmorton served with the 198th Infantry, part of the Americal Division, in the Central Highlands near Chu Lai, South Vietnam, from September 1968-September 1969.
    Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Vietnam Project.
  - David Kipfinger, circa 2018; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_226, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0065.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0066.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0067.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 176-9
    Enlisted in U.S. Army in January, 1966. In December 1967 was sent to Vietnam as an infantryman with the 1st Air Cavalry. In December 1968 he trained as a a scout and was sent to An Khe, participating in patrols in the Bong Son Plain in the Central Highlands. Later served as a machine gunner in the A Shau Valley, where he was wounded and also suffered from heat stroke. He was sent to the rear to recover. When he was sent back to his unit they were pinned down for a month by NVA artillery fire near Quang Tri, with little resupply, but finally relieved by repeated airstrikes on the NVA positions. "Any person who has been in combat and comes back suffers in some way from PSTD. They have seen or heard or been involved with something that was very difficult to get rid of." Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Veterans Project.
    Oral history is open for research. As it requires advance preparation for use, please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use this material.
  - Warren Richardson, circa 2019; 3 items 1 print; 2 CDs (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_227, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0068.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0069.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 178-7
    Drafted into U.S. Army in November, 1969. Trained with Aviation as a helicopter mechanic, maintaining CH47 (Chinook) helicopters (the larger ones with two rotors). He was sent to Vietnam in July, 1970, where he was assigned to the Americal Division at Chu Lai. He repaired Chinooks that were shot up, and did routine maintenance, and when not otherwise occupied, served as a door gunner or navigator on those same helicopters. Left service in July, 1971. Oral history accompanies this print. Part of the Veterans Project.
  - Curtis Millner, circa 2019; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_228, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0070.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0071.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0072.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 178-16
    Joined U.S. Army in 1970, "because of a broken heart." Only 17 at the time, he altered his birth certificate to make him appear to be 18. After basic training, he was sent to Ft. Belvoir and trained as a truck and large equipment mechanic. He worked with the 17th Combat Engineers for 18 months at Ft. Hood, Texas. Was sent to Vietnam and was stationed at Cam Ranh Bay with the 577th Engineers. He was later made Sgt. of the Guard at Long Binh, in charge of five miles of perimeter around that base, the largest U.S. base in Vietnam, subject to daily rocket and mortar attacks and attempts by the NVA to overrun the base. After his time in Vietnam he spent nine more years in service, with tours in Germany and Korea. Was promoted to Warrant Officer and retired in 1983.
  - Armin Barnett, Halifax County, Virginia, 2019 June; 4 items 1 print; 3 CDs (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_229, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0073.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0074.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0075.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 177-7
    Armin Barrett, born in Chicago and educated at the University of Virginia, returned to Chicago and served a four year apprenticeship in violin making at Kenneth Warren and Son, a long established instrument making shop. He opened his own shop in Seattle in 1977 and continues now to repair and make violins, violas and cellos. An accomplished musician in the Irish-American genre as well as American "old time" music, Armin primarily plays fiddle, but also banjo and guitar. He knows and has played with the most famous players in the world. A longtime friend, Armin is possessed of a wonderful sense of humor and a direct but compelling nature.
    Oral history accompanies this portrait.
  - Armin Barrett and Kinney Rorrer, Blairs, Virginia, 2019 June (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_230)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 177-24
    Kinney Rorrer is a historian and musicologist. Posey Rorrer, his great uncle, was the fiddle player in Charlie Poole's band the New North Carolina Ramblers, who recorded hit records for Victor in the 1920s. Kinney plays banjo in the style of Charlie Poole, and the banjo he is holding (which he plays regularly) belonged to Charlie Poole.
  - Armin Barrett and his partner, Shierry Nicholsen, a psychoanalyst. Both live in Seattle., 2019 May (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_231)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 177-18
  - Apprenti boulanger (Elise Lloyd), 2018 (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_232)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 174-15
  - Claude Dewey Boswell, Pittsylvania County, Virginia, 1975 (Box 14, Image RL00043_P_233)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 84-39
    Dewey Boswell was my maternal grandmother's brother, the youngest of five, born in 1899. During Prohibition he made and sold white liquor. He played clawhammer banjo in an "old time" band that he and his brothers formed before World War I. Later he farmed and worked as a housepainter.
  - William Cabell Shotwell, Halifax County, Virginia, 2019 September (Box 16, Image RL00043_P_244, Digital-materials RL.00043-SET-0001u, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0076.MP3, Audio-file RL00043-CD-0077.MP3)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 178-26.
    William Shotwell grew up on a tobacco farm in the Virgilina Community of Halifax County, Virginia. He was drafted into service in 1966 and spent most of 1967 and 1968 with the 185th Light Maintenance Battalion, stationed at Long Binh, the largest American base in Vietnam, just north of Saigon. He worked as a maintenance mechanic at Long Binh and participated in numerous search and destroy missions after the Tet offensive of 1968.
    An oral history and release form accompany this print. Part of the Vietnam Veterans Project.
    Part of the collection is restricted: original audio disks are closed to use.
  - Frank Joseph Wilcosky, Jr. and his brother, Timothy Wilcosky, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 2020 August (Box 16, Image RL00043_P_246)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 180-12
    Joe and Tim have been very close since childhood. Tim earned his undergraduate degree from Duke University in zoology in 1971. He then earned a degree from Ohio State University in Preventive Medicine, followed by his degree in Public Medicine (epidemiology) from UNC. Tim worked as an epidemiologist until his retirement.
  - Dr. Ralph Stanley on his tour bus, Ferrum, Virginia, 2001 October (Box 16, Image RL00043_P_247)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 31-19A
    Roddy Moore, director of the Blue Ridge Institute at Ferrum College, asked me to photograph Ralph Stanley while he and his band were playing at the Ferrum folklife festival. This photograph was taken on his bus after he had played an hour-long show outside in freezing weather under an open sided tent. He was not happy that he was expected to play under such conditions and was warming himself with a down comforter before autographing CDs. He said, however, that after so many years on the road, he had come to expect just about anything and that he was looking forward to a more comfortable venue at his next concert in Tallahasee, Florida the following day.
  - Rud Shupik, Callands, Virginia, 2001 (Box 16, Image RL00043_P_248)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 46-35.
    Rud Shupik plays Delta blues and rhythm and blues. He also operates an organic farm where he raises hogs and chickens which he sells at farmer's markets.
  - Wyatt Oakes and his sister, Virginia Oakes Edwards at their homeplace, Callands, Virginia, 2001 (Box 16, Image RL00043_P_249)
    Orig. print number: JA/POR 67-44
    Wyatt Oakes farmed tobacco on his family farm in the Callands community of Pittsylvania County, Virginia. He served in the Korean conflict as an infantryman, 1952-53. He would never consent to an oral history but was a great neighbor and grew beautiful tobacco. Mr. Oakes introduced me to Rogers Royal, another local tobacco farmer who still cured his tobacco with wood - the last farmer in Pittsylvania County to do so. (See portraits of Royal in the Virginia series)
- Train Project, View from Amtrak Northeast Regional, Train #147, 2010; 1.0 Linear Feet 31 prints
  These 31 11x14 inch black-and-white gelatin silver images were taken by photographer Jesse Pyrant Andrews on November 19, 2010 during a train trip from New York City to Lynchburg, Virginia. Images were chiefly taken from the windows of the moving train and captured overpasses, traffic, graffiti, residential neighborhoods, train stations, and other urban landscapes. A few shots focus on train passengers and there is one of a railroad worker on the tracks, as well as the photographer's self-portrait.
  Prints are untitled; descriptions in brackets have been supplied by library staff. All of the photographs were printed in 2011 and 2012. Original print numbers assigned by the photographer have been retained, and each print has been given an institutional identifier. Prints are arranged in order as originally received.
  - [Tracks underneath power lines], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_056)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_110_3A_4
  - [Boat on large river, bridge in distance], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_057)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_110_33
  - [Graffiti reading "Depression"], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_058)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_24
  - [Woman sleeping in window seat on train], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_059)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_1A
  - [Graffiti beneath highway pillars], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_060)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_109_12A
  - [Houses and street with white car], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_061)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_110_21A
  - [Cars on highway and graffiti], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_062)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_109_30A
  - [Large graffiti on factory wall], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_063)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_17
  - [Large river and cars on highway], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_064)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_37
  - [Bare trees and field beyond], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_065)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_6
  - [Tall grasses and weeds underneath highway from moving train], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_066)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_7
  - [Cemetery and trees from moving train], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_067)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_30A
  - [River and trees next to tracks], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_068)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_7A_8
  - [Tracks and white structure with graffiti beneath overpass], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_069)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_25A_26
  - [Abandoned building with many glass windows], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 3, Image RL00043_P_070)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_15
  - ["Sale Lease" sign behind wire], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_071)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_109_6A
  - [Fence and clouds framed by interior train window], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_072)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_36
  - [Narrow tree-lined canal and buildings beyond, from overpass], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_073)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_27
  - [White wall with graffiti, factories in distance], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_074)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_30
  - [Street with parked cars and church], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_075)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_19
  - [Crane and houses behind sheet metal fence with graffiti], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_076)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_25
  - [Globe Dye Works sign on factory roof behind trees], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_077)
  - [Line of attached houses, tracks in foreground], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_078)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_111_13A
  - [Graffiti on wall, trees and power lines beyond], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_079)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_16
  - [Stone prison-like structure with corner tower, barbed wire fence], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_080)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_14
  - [Highway ramp and avenue running through town], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_081)
    Orig. print number: JA_LAL_108_20
  - [Overhead view of tree-lined tracks], 2010 Nov. 19 (Box 4, Image RL00043_P_082)